Welcome to close enough floor where I [kilian] tell backstories that might not be entirely correct
but they are
Close enough [on] today's episode the destinies Backstory a giant space ball ship docked on
Civilization called the Alixe knee and gave them technology and shit then he said you know, what guys I'm out of here
What why we love you and worship you and Whatnot yes?
and if I was clean people
I would have stayed with my ex-girlfriend
[also], your TV series shitty soda giant ball Gerald across the Galaxy to our solar system and met up with Humans hi humans
I'm thinking I could advance her technology by hundreds of years listen, buddy
I got this similar email a couple of months ago now. It wasn't about Advancing technology
It was about advancing my dick and now I'm sterile. Yeah, I'm not an email. I'm a giant space ball, okay?
I'll believe you
But remember if this is fake [I] have a really good lawyer the space ball also called the traveler did a bunch of great stuff?
It's terraformed planets and made human life span three times as long
It's created world peace and improved steam tech support humans with their new technology travel the stars
I met up [with] [our] old friends
who are you yadi [licks] knee, but no one can remember that so you can call us the [Fallen] the
[fallen], what are you 12? Okay? [mmM]? Okay? We are at war
[now] toward the Humans everything was great
Then everything went to shit something called the darkness was chasing the traveler and completely destroying everything in its path
Why?
Well according to the latest DLC the traveler had lots of unpaid parking tickets
Then a [buncha] insecure space nazis took over Mars and [Mercury] turned into robots
I'm not even gonna try to explain that one the travelers sacrifice itself to defeat the darkness because it loved
Humans and
Even more so Netflix then it became a coma patient [the] humans didn't I built a city under it called the last city
They wanted to call it this city
But then they decide to go with something a bit more creative
Before the giant space ball became a vegetable it created a small hail of robots, it's even had respected actors to play them
But apparently it didn't pay them enough to give a shit
The Robots mission is to revive the dead then the dead people become guardians glass city
Obviously around that person that has no connection to the last city and no reason to protected
It's not really the person you want protecting the last bastion of human civilization
But the last city has like no unemployment and being a guardian is a minim which high-risk job
I'm saying blast city is inhabited [by] a bunch of lazy counts one of these small robots
Charm to Russia and revive a dead guy. Oh, wow I found you
[this] place is dangerous and
This crap [I] come with me
the guy that robot found is you like subscribe check out my parodies more importantly and
new Recap next week